A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial Press Office, Series 3 FA456
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Gubernatorial Press Office, 3; 10.8 Cubic Feet 9 record storage cartons.
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs Assemblyman Burns' Bill, 1964 March 20; 1008.15/3431 (Box 5)
  - Governor's Mansion, Michel Legendre, 1964 March 23; 1008.15/3432 - 1008.15/3434 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Proclamation for Senior Citizen's Month, Mrs. Levy, 1964 March 24; 1008.15/3435 - 1008.15/3438 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Southern Tier Expressway Group, 1964 April 14; 1008.15/3439 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Robert Feinberg, 1964 April 15; 1008.15/3440 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Governor of Buenos Aires, Dr. Anselmo Marini, 1964 April 16; 1008.15/3441 - 1008.15/3442 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Malcolm Wilson, Nurses Week Proclamation, 1964 April 16; 1008.15/3443 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Maple Queen, Linda Markham, Mrs. Markham, Don Haight, Ransom Crosby, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1964 April 16; 1008.15/3444 - 1008.15/3449 (Box 5)
  - Capitol steps, Minneapolis Lutheran Choir, 1964 April 21; 1008.15/3450 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Mr. Aldrich presents proclamation for recreation month, 1964 May 7; 1008.15/3451 (Box 5)
  - Saratoga Performing Arts Center, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Laurance Rockefeller, Ground Breaking Ceremony, 1964 June 30; 1008.15/3452 - 1008.15/3464 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Mr. Wagoner and group, 1964 July 23; 1008.15/3465 - 1008.15/3466 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Red Cross Fund Drive, 1964 September 25; 1008.15/3467 - 1008.15/3469 (Box 5)
  - Capitol, Nelson A. Rockefeller seals time capsul, 1964 October 26; 1008.15/3470 - 1008.15/3474 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Muscular Dystrophy Poster Child, 1964 October 26; 1008.15/3475 - 1008.15/3478 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Lion's Club Blind Seal Campaign, 1964 October 26; 1008.15/3479 (Box 5)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller tours storm area, 1964 December 6; 1008.15/3480 - 1008.15/3503 (Box 5)
  - Albany, School Board Conferees, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, Donald Gray, Mrs. John Mallory, Alice Foley, Everett Dyer, G. Howard Gold, 1964 December 7; 1008.15/3504 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, TV men, 1964 December 9; 1008.15/3505 - 1008.15/3506 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Seventh Day Adventists, 1964 December 16; 1008.15/3507 - 1008.15/3509 (Box 5)
  - Statewide Educational Television Network, Nelson A. Rockefeller, James Allen, Jr., Samuel B. Gould, 1964 December 18; 1008.15/3508 (Box 5)
  - Opening of Computer Center AESOB, 1964 December 22; 1008.15/3510 - 1008.15/3516 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Route 17 Expressway, Hyman Mintz, William Smith, Jr., Charles Henderson, Barber Conable, Richard Marshall, James Hastings, Bruce Manley, Richard Lounsberry, Jeremiah Moriarty, George Ingalls, 1964 December 22; 1008.15/3518 - 1008.15/3519 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Reapportionment bill, Senator Robert McEwen, Senator Barber Conable, Jr., 1964 December 23; 1008.15/3517 (Box 5)
  - Queensboro Chamber of Commerce, 1966; 1008.15/1490 - 1008.15/1494 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Freedom Foundation Awards, 1966; 1008.15/1787 (Box 5)
  - Executive Mansion, Open House, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, Louis Lefkowitz, General O'Hara, 1966 January 1; 1008.15/1416 - 1008.15/1439 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. rules and regulations for police basic training, 1966 January 4; 1008.15/1440 - 1008.15/1447 (Box 5)
  - Opening of Legislature, Nelson A. Rockefeller at podium, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller in audience, 1966 January 5; 1008.15/1448 - 1008.15/1467 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Vanhare, school group, 1966 January 10; 1008.15/1468 (Box 5)
  - Conference Room, New York State Association for Mental Health, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Conklin, 1966 January 10; 1008.15/1469 (Box 5)
  - Statler Wilton Hotel, Washington DC, National Wildlife Federation, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1966 January 11; 1008.15/1470 - 1008.15/1471 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller presents Service Cross to Mrs. Kolenberg, General O'Hara, Jack Leary, Norris Paxton, Frank Votto, 1966 January 11; 1008.15/1472 -1008.15/1477 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Heart Fund Drive, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Campbell, Mike Sulsi, 1966 January 17; 1008.15/1478 (Box 5)
  - State Police Campus, Open House, 1966 January 17; 1008.15/1479 - 1008.15/1485 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs one hundred million dollar bill for New York City, 1966 January 18; 1008.15/1486 - 1008.15/1487 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Conservation Appointments, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Dr. Mason Lawrence, Cecil Heacox, Robert Young, Leighton Hope, Mr. Kilborne, Dr. Lawrence, Mr. Heacox, 1966 January 21; 1008.15/1537 - 1008.15/1542 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Senator Marchi, Assemblyman Amann, Assemblyman Russo, 1966 January 25; 1008.15/1488 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Art Contest Winner, Christina DeMarco, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mayor Corning, 1966 January 28; 1008.15/1489 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs USO Proclamation, 1966 February 1; 1008.15/1495 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller Health and Mental Hygiene, 1966 February 1; 1008.15/1496 - 1008.15/1504 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Budget Hearing, 1966 February 1; 1008.15/1505 - 1008.15/1507 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Teacher Recognition Day, 1966 February 2; 1008.15/1508 - 1008.15/1511 (Box 5)
  - DeWitt Clinton Hotel, VFW Banquet, 1966 February 7; 1008.15/1512 - 1008.15/1526 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller presents Boy Scout Awards, 1966 February 7; 1008.15/1527 - 1008.15/1533 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Jackie Robinson, 1966 February 8; 1008.15/1534 - 1008.15/1536 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Queens County American Legion, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Edward Connors, Frank Moriarity, John Ardiff, Richard Stapleton, Ramone Tinagero, William Carr, Melvin Wolinsky, Al Maickel, Louis Marconi, William Rigney, Al Nienstedt, John F. Keenan, 1966 February 14; 1008.15/1543 - 1008.15/1544 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Webster NY Young Republicans, 1966 February 14; 1008.15/1545 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller receives American Legion Poppy flower from Mrs. William R. Peabody, 1966 February 14; 1008.15/1546 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Route 17 Association meeting, Gordon Wackett, Leo Ritz, William Harrison, Ben Kaplan, William Taylor, Robert Taylor, Edwin Underbill, Joseph Sullivan, John Bates, Charles Heeman, Grey Fitzpatrick, Kirk Claghorn, James Grimm, Senator Anderson, Senator Smith, Senator Newcombe, Senator Niles, Assemblyman Present, Assemblyman Manley, Assemblyman Walkley, Assemblyman Marshall, Assemblyman Henderson, Assemblyman Ingalls, Assemblyman Mason, Assemblyman McBride, Assemblyman Boland, Mrs. Cook, 1966 February 14; 1008.15/1547 - 1008.15/1556 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Constance Cooke, Burch McMorran, 1966 February 14; 1008.15/1557 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, New York University and Inter-American Law Institute Law Students, 1966 February 15; 1008.15/1558 (Box 5)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Group from Malone, NY, Senator Staffords, Donald Stone, 1966 February 15; 1008.15/1559 (Box 5)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Red Room, Swearing in Alan Miller, Commissioner of Mental, 1966 February 21 (Box 5)
  - Hygiene, 1008.15/1560 - 1008.15/1563 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller receives First Murray R. Nathan Award from the Albany Community Chest and Red Cross, 1966 February 21; 1008.15/1564 - 1008.15/1566 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Bartlett, school group, 1966 February 21; 1008.15/1567 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Teenage Republican Club of Scarsdale, NY, Scarsdale Young Democrats, 1966 February 21; 1008.15/1568 - 1008.15/1570 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Louis Lefkowitz, Business and Professional Women Representatives, 1966 February 21; 1008.15/1571 - 1008.15/1572 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Assemblyman Duryen, school group, 1966 February 21; 1008.15/1573 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Dr. Sandy Ray, 1966 February 22; 1008.15/1574 - 1008.15/1580 (Box 5)
  - Emmanuel Baptist Church, State Street, Albany, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1966 February 22; 1008.15/1581 - 1008.15/1584 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Jerome Schutzer and constituents, 1966 February 22; 1008.15/1585 - 1008.15/1587 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator LaVerne, girl scouts of Rochester, 1966 February 22; 1008.15/1588 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Martin Ginsberg, family groups, 1966 February 22; 1008.15/1589 - 1008.15/1592 (Box 5)
  - Room 414 Senate Chamber, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator William E. Adams, 1966 February 22; 1008.15/1593 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Councilman Ned Regan, 1966 February 22; 1008.15/1594 (Box 5)
  - Governor's Mansion, Legislative Reception, 1966 February 22; 1008.15/1595 - 1008.15/1607 (Box 5)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Conklin, Handicapped Workers, 1966 February 28; 1008.15/1608 - 1008.15/1609 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, New York State Council of Churches, 1966 February 28; 1008.15/1610 - 1008.15/1612 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 4-H Capitol Day, 1966 February 28; 1008.15/1613 - 1008.15/1626 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Easter Seal Child, 1966 March 1; 1008.15/1627 - 1008.15/1628 (Box 5)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Michael Scelsi, John Tieder, 1966 March 7; 1008.15/1629 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Pisani and Paycheck Group, 1966 March 7; 1008.15/1630 - 1008.15/1631 (Box 5)
  - Conference Room, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Department of Health group, 1966 March 7; 1008.15/1632 (Box 5)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller. John Tieder and family, Cameroon Foreign Exchange Student, 1966 March 7; 1008.15/1633 - 1008.15/1635 (Box 5)
  - National Girl Scout Week, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Wendy Ellenbogen, Heather Lynn Halsted, Priscilla Mary Reed, Loretta Agnes Preska, 1966 March 7; 1008.15/1636 - 1008.15/1637 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Citizen's Committee for Children, Reverend Moran Weston, Mrs. Ascoli, Edith Alt, Auren Kahn, Ed Ross, Professor Frank Van Dyke, Jacqueline Zaslow, Harry Becker, Betty Bernstein, Val Mour Ouellette, 1966 March 7; 1008.15/1638 (Box 5)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller signs Waterloo Proclamation, 1966 March 7; 1008.15/1639 - 1008.15/1644 (Box 5)
  - Governor's Mansion, Weekly News Publishers at Executive Mansion, Malcolm Wilson, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Lefkowitz, others, 1966 March 7; 1008.15/1645 - 1008.15/1650 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Earl Brydges, girls, 1966 March 8; 1008.15/1651 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Farm Group, 1966 March 8; 1008.15/1652 - 1008.15/1657 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Frank Tarck, 1966 March 8; 1008.15/1658 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Bartlett, Westport students, 1966 March 8; 1008.15/1659 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Stafford, St. Lawrence University Government class, 1966 March 8; 1008.15/1660 (Box 5)
  - Capitol, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Nathan Goldberg, Jewish War Veterans, 1966 March 8; 1008.15/1661 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. West Point Proclamation, Robert Kren, 1966 March 8; 1008.15/1662 - 1008.15/1664 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, District Attorney's group, 1966 March 14; 1008.15/1665 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Joseph Finley, Wayne County students, 1966 March 14; 1008.15/1666 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Hanna, Mrs. Hanna and sons, Edward Jr. and Paul, 1966 March 14; 1008.15/1667 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Bankers, 1966 March 14; 1008.15/1668 - 1008.15/1670 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Garfinkel's family, 1966 March 14; 1008.15/1671 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs bill, Senator Lombardi of Canastota, 1966 March 15; 1008.15/1672 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Malcolm Wilson, Senator Mackell, 1966 March 15; 1008.15/1673 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Coleman, Gompres High School students, 1966 March 15; 1008.15/1674 - 1008.15/1676 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Cities Teacher Association of New York, 1966 March 15; 1008.15/1677 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Wolfe, Champlain Central School Group, 1966 March 15; 1008.15/1678 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Walter Clark, North Country School, Lake Placid students, 1966 March 15; 1008.15/1679 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Women's Forum, 1966 March 15; 1008.15/1680 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Elaine Sulka, 1966 March 15; 1008.15/1681 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, John J. Delaney, 1966 March 15; 1008.15/1682 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Kurmel, Senator Lentol, Proclamation of the Millenium of Polish Christianity, 1966 March 21; 1008.15/1683 - 1008.15/1684 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller receivs honorary card from New York Automobile Association, George M Frauenheim, Lester J. Parnell, Joseph Pentak, Dr. Harry Pratt, 1966 March 21; 1008.15/1685 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Mabel Knapp, 1966 March 21; 1008.15/1686 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Chester Hardt and group, 1966 March 21; 1008.15/1687 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator James Donovan, Clinton High School students, 1966 March 21; 1008.15/1688 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, John Hiltz, Red Cross Proclamation, 1966 March 21; 1008.15/1689 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Theodore Roosevelt New York City oration finalists, 1966 March 21; 1008.15/1690 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs police retirement bill, 1966 March 22; 1008.15/1691 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs bill for Geoffrey Chandler Drive, Senator Newcomb, Assemblyman Kenneth L. Wilson, 1966 March 22; 1008.15/1692 (Box 5)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Nassau County Republican Delegates, 1966 March 28; 1008.15/1693 (Box 5)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller, New York State Home Building Association, 1966 March 28; 1008.15/1694 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, group for student activity day, 1966 March 29; 1008.15/1695 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Civil Service Pay Raise Bill, 1966 March 29; 1008.15/1696 - 1008.15/1704 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller swearing in Judge Eugene Goddard, 1966 March 29; 1008.15/1705 - 1008.15/1706 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Republican women, 1966 March 29; 1008.15/1707 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs cancer crusade proclamation for month of April, 1966 March 29; 1008.15/1708 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Joe Boyd, 1966 March 29; 1008.15/1709 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Joy Henschel, Japanese students, 1966 March 29; 1008.15/1710 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Teachers for Rockefeller, 1966 March 29; 1008.15/1711 - 1008.15/1712 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. swearing in Judge John Reilly, 1966 March 31; 1008.15/1713 - 1008.15/1714 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Nurses Proclamation, 1966 April 18; 1008.15/1715 (Box 5)
  - Governor's Mansion, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1966 April 19; 1008.15/1716 - 1008.15/1718 (Box 5)
  - Governor's Mansion, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, local newspaper women, 1966 April 19; 1008.15/1719 - 1008.15/1732 (Box 5)
  - Conference Room, Nelson A. Rockefeller, NYS. Association Mental Health, 1966 April 25; 1008.15/1733 - 1008.15/1734 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Rosalie Ellen Carpenter NYS's Maple Queen, 1966 April 25; 1008.15/1735 - 1008.15/1739 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Charles Hagg and family, 1966 April 27; 1008.15/1740 (Box 5)
  - Red Room. Public Works Week Proclamation, Joe Ronan, 1966 May 9; 1008.15/1741 (Box 6)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Tulip Ball, Richard Meyer, Arthur Brumazkish, 1966 May 9; 1008.15/1742 (Box 6)
  - Governor's Mansion, Interdepartmental Meeting, Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1966 May 9; 1008.15/1743 (Box 6)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller presents Special Award to Lowell Adams, Senator James Hastings, Mr. and Mrs. Lowell C. Adams, 1966 May 9; 1008.15/1744 (Box 6)
  - Capitol steps, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Assemblyman Kolyman, H. Shaffer, 1966 May 11; 1008.15/1745 (Box 6)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller signs Veterans of Foreign Wars Bill, Assemblyman Louis DeSalvio, Malcolm Wilson, Assemblyman DeMessimn, 1966 May 23; 1008.15/1746 (Box 6)
  - Red Room. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mrs. Nelson A. Rockefeller, Senator Brydges, E. Dent Lackey the Mayor of Niagara Falls, 1966 May 24; 1008.15/1747 (Box 6)
  - New York City, 1966 May 24
    - Governor Rockefeller addresses 100 key workers for the united Jewish Appeal of Greater New York at 220 west 58th St. NY City, 1966 May 24; 1008.15/Roll524A-524C (Box 6)
      - Governor arrives at UJA greeted by members of the board of directors (Roll 524A, Frame 1-2)
      - with Louis Lefkowitz (Roll 524A, Frame 3)
      - with Securities and Exchange Commission chairman Manuel Cohen (Roll 524A, Frame 4)
      - listening to address of UJA people (Roll 524A, Frame 5-8)
      - addressing members of UJA (Roll 524B, Frame 1-5)
      - listening to address of UJA (Roll 524B, Frame 6)
      - Governor makes solicitation via phone for funds for the United Jewish Appeal (Roll 524B, Frame 7-12)
      - with Manuel Cohen, chairman Securities and Exchange Commission (Roll 524C, Frame 1-4)
      - unidentified (Roll 524C, Frame 5)
      - Paula Tolchin of Manhattan (Roll 524C, Frame 6)
      - unidentified (Roll 524C, Frame 7-8)
      - with Sam Leidersdorf (Roll 524C, Frame 9)
      - unidentified (Roll 524C, Frame 10-11)
      - Governor departs building (Roll 524C, Frame 12)
  - Albany, NY, Press Conference, 1966 May 25; 1008.15/Roll525; (15) (Box 6)
  - New York City, 1966 May 26
    - Governor Rockefeller's Conference on Women. New York Hilton Hotel, 1966 May 26; 1008.15/Roll526A-526G (Box 6)
      Scope and Contents note
      Presented in cooperation with The New York State Woman's Council and The State Interdepartmental Women's Committee
      - Governor is greeted on arrival at the Hilton Hotel by Carolyn Hood of the Rockefeller Center Incorporated and Margot Herman of McCann Rickson advertising agency (Roll 526A, Frame 1-2)
      - Pete McQue (Roll 526A, Frame 3)
      - unidentified (Roll 526A, Frame 4-9)
      - Cay Barnes, Hollis, New York (Roll 526A, Frame 10-11)
      - prior to making statement at press conference (Roll 526A, Frame 12)
      - Governor holds press conference (Roll 526B, Frame 1-6)
      - Spanish speaking women grouped (Roll 526B, Frame 7-9)
      - unidentified (Roll 526B, Frame 10)
      - Guin (Eq) Hall, Co-Chairman (Roll 526B, Frame 11-12)
      - Entire roll includes general views of Governor talking and greeting participants of Governors Conference on Women (Roll 526C)
      - greeted by Kitty Carlisle (Roll 526E, Frame 1)
      - governor received citation from Roselou Flanagan, president, on behalf of Advertising Women in New York (Roll 526E, Frame 2-3)
      - Governor receives Plaque from Mrs. Louise Fisher Morris, president, on behalf of the Utility Club (Roll 526E, Frame 4-5)
      - with Kitty Carlisle (Roll 526E, Frame 6)
      - Governor and Kitty Carlisle listen to report of first day's session of conferences (Roll 526E, Frame 7-8)
      - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller at dinner of Conf. on Women (Roll 526E)
        - unidentified (Roll 526F, Frame 1-3)
        - with members of Board of Conf. on Women, center is Mrs. Michael Detar, President, The Council of European Women in Exile, 143-13, Beech Avenue, Flushing, Long Island (Roll 526F, Frame 4-5)
        - Governor, Mrs. Rockefeller, and Kitty Carlisle (Roll 526F, Frame 6-7)
        - Governor, Mrs. Rockefeller, and Louis Lefkowitz (Roll 526F, Frame 8)
        - Governor addresses dinner (Roll 526F, Frame 10-12)
        - Governor addresses dinner (Roll 526G, Frame 1-2)
        - with Rita Stafford, of Hunter College (Roll 526G, Frame 3-4)
    - Governor and Mrs. Rockefeller attended United Cerebral Palsy of Queens Testimonial Dinner, 1008.15/Roll526H-526J (Box 6)
      - unidentified (Roll 526J, Frame 1)
      - Governor, Mrs. Rockefeller, Louis J. Lefkowitz, Sean Keating, Master of Ceremonies, Robert T. Groh, Dinner Chairman, Mr. & Mrs. Nat H. Hebtel (Roll 526J, Frame 2-8)
      - same as above (Roll 526H, Frame 1-7)
      - with Rabbi Forman (Roll 526H, Frame 8)
    - untitled, 1008.15/Roll526; (10) (Box 6)
  - Hilton Hotel. NY City, 1966 May 27 (Box 6)
    - Governor Rockefeller attends luncheon and final meeting of the Governor's Conference on Women at the Hilton Hotel, 1966 May 27; 1008.15/Roll527A-527B (Box 6)
      - Neil Stafford (Roll 527A, Frame 1)
      - Gwen Hall, chairman of the conference (Roll 527A, Frame 2-3)
      - Emily Caloyer, Mrs. Anna Tuthill, West Branch, New York (Roll 527A, Frame 4-5)
      - Mrs. Charlotte Brown Myers, Education director, Standard Oil, N.J. Dr. Eugene Laubach, executive director, Riverside Church (Roll 527A, Frame 6-7)
      - Kitty Carlisle, Governor, and Mrs. Hall (Roll 527A, Frame 7-8)
      - Louis Lefkowitz addressing group (Roll 527A, Frame 9-10)
      - General views of Hilton gathering (Roll 527A, Frame 11-12)
      - Gwen Hall, chairman of the Governors Conference on Women, Louis Lefkowitz, and Governor Rockefeller (Roll 527B, Frame 1-2)
      - Governor addressing women (Roll 527B, Frame 3-5)
      - Louise Alexander (Roll 527B, Frame 6)
      - Nancy King (Roll 527B, Frame 7)
      - unidentified (Roll 527B, Frame 8)
      - Vera Allan of Bronx; Horenda Ravett of Queens; Mary Tobin, Yonkers, New York (Mrs. Hall's Asst.). (Roll 527B, Frame 9)
      - Nina Jones of the Governors staff (Roll 527B, Frame 11-12)
  - Cornerstone Baptist Church, Brooklyn, NY, 1966 May 29 (Box 6)
    - Governor Rockefeller at Cornerstone Baptist Church, Brooklyn NY and Hotel Hilton NY Elks meeting, 1966 May 29; 1008.15/Roll529A-529D (Box 6)
      - arriving at the church entrance (Roll 529A, Frame 1)
      - blank (Roll 529A, Frame 2)
      - incl. Governor Rockefeller speaking at the church service (Roll 529A, Frame 3-12)
      - Governor speaking at the service. At left is Pastor Rev. Sandy F. Ray (Roll 529B, Frame 1)
      - Governor with Members of the congregation after the service (Roll 529B, Frame 2)
      - blank (Roll 529B, Frame 3)
      - Governor autographing after the church service (Roll 529B, Frame 4-6)
      - Governor with Pastor Dr. Sandy F. Ray... (Roll 529B, Frame 7)
      - Left to Right - Mrs. William F. Ray of Dallas Texas... (Roll 529B, Frame 8-9)
      - Governor Rockefeller... Miss Rue Zalia Watkins, granddaughter of Dr. Sandy F. Ray... and Dr. Sandy F. Ray pastor of the church (Roll 529B, Frame 10)
      - Dr. Sandy F. Ray and Governor Rockefeller after the service and inspection of the new hall (Roll 529B, Frame 11-12)
      - Governor at Elks meeting..., 1008.15/Roll529C-529D (Box 6)
        - suggest ignore this as he is not wearing Elks insignia (Roll 529C, Frame 1)
        - Warren Gardner may like this one... (Roll 529C, Frame 2)
        - Governor and {blank} (ask WG for ident) (Roll 529C, Frame 3)
        - Governor speaking (Roll 529C, Frame 4-5)
        - Hopson R. Reynolds, Grand Exalted Ruler and Governor (Roll 529C, Frame 6-8)
        - Governor and Mrs. Evelyn Reynolds (Roll 529C, Frame 9-10)
        - Reynolds... Governor and Mrs. Nettie B. Smith Grand Daughter of Elks... (Roll 529C, Frame 11)